J. Peter Lesley Papers 1826-1898 Mss.B.L56
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. General correspondence, 1826-1898 (Box 1)
  - Addressed Envelope to the Secretaries of the Philosophical Society..., 1862 Feb. 18; Murchison, Roderick Impey, Sir, 1792-1871 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1862 March. 8; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1862 March 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1862 March 21; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Benjamin Smith Lyman, 1862 April 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April 10; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Charles Sumner, 1862 April 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April 14; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to James D. Dana, 1862 April 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to James D. Dana, 1862 April 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April 21; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Andrew Carnegie, 1862 April 21; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April 23; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to James D. Dana, 1862 April 23; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April 26; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 April? Sat.; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 May 3; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to the Librarian of the American Philosophical Society, 1862 May 3; Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 May 8; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Mr. Hunt, 1862 May 12; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 May 15; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1862 May 28; Henry, Joseph (Box 7)
  - to Joseph Henry, 1862 May 30; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 June 2; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1862 Sept. 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 Sept. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 Sept. 13; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 Sept. 23; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to Mr. Blackwell, 1862 Nov. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to Thomas S. Hunt, 1862 Nov. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to Benjamin Smith Lyman, 1862 Nov. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to Mr. Blackwell, 1862 Nov. 9; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1862 Dec. 17; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Jan. 22; Wilson, Daniel (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Jan. 31; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to Thomas E. Blackwell, 1863 Feb. 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Feb. 15; Whitney, J. D. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Feb. 20; Henderson, A. A. (Box 7)
  - to Miss Annie E. Hall, 1863 March 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to Henry Wilson, 1863 March 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 March 9; Silliman, Benjamin, Jr. (Box 7)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1863 March 12; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 April 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 April 25; Dawson, J. W. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 April 27; Dawson, J. W. (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, Librarian of the American Philosophical Society, 1863 May 6; Quincy, Josiah (Box 7)
  - to Benjamin S. Lyman, 1863 May 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 May 10; Haidinger, W. F. (Box 7)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1863 May 18; Revere, Josie (Box 7)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1863 May 30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to A. D. Bache, 1863 June 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 June 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863? June 6; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 June 6; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 July 15; Haidinger, W. F. (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 July 19; Dawson, J. W. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Aug. 20; Haldeman, Samuel Stehman, 1812-1880 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to W. P. Schimper, 1863 Sept. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 19; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Sept. 25; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 25; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 26; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to Mrs. Susan Lesley, 1863 Sept. 26; Child, Lydia Maria, 1802-1880 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Sept. 27; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Sept. 28; Carey, Henry (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Oct. 2; Worther, A. H. (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Oct. 18; Lyell, Charles, Sir, 1797-1875 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Oct. 20; Maskelyne, Nevil A. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Oct. 21; Sedgwick, Adam, 1785-1873 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Oct. 22; Hooker, W. H. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 3; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 9; Des Moulin, Charles. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 9; Kendall, E. O.. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 13; Garnier, C. F. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 20; Bache, A.D., (Alexander Dallas), 1806-1867 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 20; Charnier, C. A. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 24; Bost, Jenny (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Nov. 25; Bost, Mary G. (Box 7)
  - "Rose from Marie Bost's Grave at Sallies, 1863 Nov.; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 7)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1863 Dec. 1; Delesse (Box 7)
  - Letter to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Dec. 1 (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Dec. 7; Bost, A. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Dec. 21; Tholuck, A. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Dec. 24; Bost, A. (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1863 Dec. 25; Bost, Sophie (Box 7)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1864 Jan. 4; Berthoud, Fritz (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1864 Jan. 29; Logan, W. E. (Box 8)
  - to P[eter] Lesley, 1864 Feb. 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [J.P. Lesley], 1864 Feb. 9; Haidinger, W. F. (Box 8)
  - to P[eter] Lesley, 1864 Feb. 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Les;e, Am. Phil. Soc., 1864 March 3; Henry, Joseph (Box 8)
  - to [J.Peter] Lesley, 1864 March 10; Genth, F. A. (Box 8)
  - to [J.P.] Lesley, 1864 March 12; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to P[eter] Lesley, 1864 April 23; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to John Amory Lowell, 1864 April 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter Lesley, 1864 May 1; Bost, Mary G. (Box 8)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1864 May 1; Henderson, A. A. (Box 8)
  - to John Amory Lowell, 1864 May 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to John A. Lowell, 1864 May 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to "Mr. Editor", 1864 June 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to L.H. Smipson, 1864 June 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report on the Warwick Properties in Bucks and Chester counties. [Private Reports], 1864 June; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [F.A.P.] Barnard, 1864 July 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report to Messrs H.G. Leisenring, Moore and others on the Harrisburgh Furnace property, 1864 July 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to L.A. MacKey, 1864 July 11; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 July 12; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to J.P.MLesley, 1864 July 18; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 8)
  - to P[eter] Lesley, 1864 July 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 July 22; Harden, J. W. (Box 8)
  - to "My dear B, 1864 July 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1864 July 22; Sparks, Jared (Box 8)
  - to [J.Peter Lesley], 1864 July 26; Desor, Edouard (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1864 Aug. 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Aug. 5; Harden, J. W. (Box 8)
  - to J. P[eter] Lesley, 1864 Aug. 17; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1864 Aug. 20; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Leslie [sic], 1864 Aug. 27; Brooks, T. B. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Aug. 27; Everett, Edward (Box 8)
  - to Tho[ma]s S. Blair(?), 1864 Sept.; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1864 Oct. 3; Langel, Augustus (Box 8)
  - to [J.Peter Lesley], 1864 Oct. 4; Tholuck, A. (Box 8)
  - to [J.Peter Lesley], 1864 Oct. 6; Tunner, P. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Oct. 7; Harden, J. W. (Box 8)
  - Report on Thomas Moore's mines, Westmoreland Count, Pa., 1864 Oct. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to John E. Devlen, 1864 Oct. 23; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Oct. 23; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - [J.P.] Lesley, 1864 Oct. 24; Langel, Augustus (Box 8)
  - Report to Mr. William E.S. Baker, 1864 Oct. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [J.Peter] Lesley, 1864 Nov. 3; Whitney, W. D. (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Hendry, 1864 Nov. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to W. D. Whitney, 1864 Nov. 4; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to "Aunt Kitty.", 1864 Nov. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Nov. 5; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Henderson, 1864 Nov. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to Mrs. Adams, 1864 Nov. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [John Morreson], 1864 Nov. 7; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report on the Boston and Picton Coal Co. Holdings to John P. Prince and Company, 1864 Nov. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report to Mssrs Evans and Haskill on the Hummelstown ore belt, 1864 Nov. 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1864 Nov. 19; Henderson, A. A. (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley, 1864 Nov. 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1864 Nov. 29; Whitney, J. D. (Box 8)
  - to Jos[eph] Henry, 1864 Dec. 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Sjeafer, 1864 Dec. 6; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Dec. 7; Henry, Joseph (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Dec. 9; Brooks, T. B. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Dec. 10; Daniels, Edward (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesle[sic], 1864 Dec. 11; Peirce, Benjamin, 1809-1880 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Dec. 17; Harden, J. W. (Box 8)
  - to [Benjamin S.] Lyman, 1864 Dec. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report on the Warner Tract on Beaver River to [Grosvenor C. Spanger?], 1864 Dec. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1864 Dec. 24; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to Leo Lesqueruex, 1864 Dec. 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - Report on the P. Kerr and Co. Coal lands, Washington County, Penna., 1864 Dec.; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Sheafer, [1864?]; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Jan. 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 Jan. 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to American Journal of Science, 1865 Jan 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [James D.] Dana, 1865 Jan. 13; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1865 Jan. 15; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [Benjamin S.] Lyman, 1865 Jan. 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Henderson, 1865 Jan. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1865 Jan. 20; Bost, John (Box 8)
  - to John M. Forbes, 1985 Jan. 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to P[eter] Lesley, 1865 Jan. 21,28,30; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - tp [J. Peter] Lesley, 1865 Jan. 23; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 8)
  - to [Benjamin S.] Lyman, 1865 Jan. 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 Jan. 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [James D.] Dana, 1865 Jan. 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Leslie (sic), 1865 Jan. 31; Francis, James J. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Jan. 31; Tyndale, Hector (Box 8)
  - to Samue]l G. Ward on the John Galloway tract, 1865 Feb. 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to "Aunt Kitty", 1865 Feb. 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Feb. 2; Harden, J. W. (Box 8)
  - [J.] P[eter] Lesley, 1865 Feb. 3; Agassiz, Louis, 1807-1873 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Feb. 5; Daniels, Edward (Box 8)
  - to Joseph Lee, 1865 Feb. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 Feb. 11; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J[oseph] Lyman, 1865 Feb. 13; Desor, Edouard (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Feb. 13; Norton, Charles Eliot, 1827-1908 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 Feb. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to Henry Ward, 1865 Feb. 19; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Feb. 23; Brooks, T. B. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 Feb. 24; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to David.S. Brown and Co. on Slipping Rock oil, 1865 March 2(?); Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to W.B. Ogden, 1865 March 2; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 March 3; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to Provost Marshall, 1865 March 3; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 March 3; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to [J. Peter] Lesley, 1865 March 6; Holbert, J. S. (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 March 7; Hall, James (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 March 15; Altman, Henry (Box 8)
  - to F.A.P. Barnard, 1865 March 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 March 23; Winchell, Alexander (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 March 24; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 March 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J.P. Lesley, 1865 April 12; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910 (Box 8)
  - to Mr. Agassiz, 1865 April 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 8)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 April 24; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910 (Box 8)
  - to [Peter Lesley], 1865 April 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 8)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 May 6; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 8; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1865 May 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to Prof. A. Winchell, 1865 May 22; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to "My dear Chauncey", 1865 May 24; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 25 ans.; Bost, Sophie (Box 9)
  - to Samuel and Sophie Bost, 1865 May 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 25; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to John Avery Lowell, 1865 May 28; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 May 28; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - Concerning the preservation of petroleum after it is removed from the earth., 1865 May 29; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 June 2; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1865 June 5; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 June 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to Leo Lesquereux, 1865 June 14; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to David S. Brown on Slipping Rock oil., 1865 June 16; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 June 25; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - Opinion to Charles Bann to accompany the report on Brady's Bend and Paint Lick report., 1865 June 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1865 June 26; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - and B. S. Lyman Report of Cape Breton Coal Beds for the International Caledonia, Clyde and Block-house Coal Companies., 1865 June 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 June 29; Agassiz, Alexander, 1835-1910 (Box 9)
  - to the Clyde Coal and Mining Company, 1865 July 1; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to Mr. Agassiz., 1865 July 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - Report to David S. Brown on the Slippery Rock Creek oil., 1865 July 10; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 July 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Aug. 11; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Aug. 15; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Aug. 16; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1865 Aug. 18; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Aug. 22; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Aug. 28; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to Samuel Bost., 1865 Sept. 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. W. Harden, 1865 Sept. 17; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Sept. 20; Haidinger, W. F. (Box 9)
  - to Benjamin S. Lyman, 1865 Sept. 25; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to "Dear Allen", 1865 Sept. 26; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Sept. 28; Boss, Theodore (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Sept. 28; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Oct. 1; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to James Hall, 1865 Oct. 8; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Oct. 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Oct. 22; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Nov. 20; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to Benjamin S. Lyman, 1865 Nov. 27; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - Memorandum..., 1865 Dec. 18; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Dec. 20; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Dec. 21; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Dec. 23; Shumard, B. F. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1865 Dec. 26; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to the President fo the Plymouth Coal Company..., 1865 Dec. 28; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1865 Dec. 29; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1856 Dec. 29; Smith, Russell (Box 9)
  - Report on lands on Paint Lick Fork of the Sandy River in Eastern Kentucky., 1865?; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to S. L. Thurlow., 1866 Jan. 6; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Jan. 10; Smith, Russell (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 2; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 5; Lyon, Sidney S. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 15; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 16; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 20; Lyon, Sidney S. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 28; Barnard, F. A. P. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Feb. 28; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 March 1; Gould, Augustus A. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 3; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 March 3; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 7; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 12; Ingham, Charles F. (Box 9)
  - Preceipt to the Plymouth Coal Company, 1866 March 12; Jones, Henry (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 13; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to S. L. Thurlow, 1866 March 14; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to Mrs. Lesley, 1866 March 14; Meigs, Charles D. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 15; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 15; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to F. A. P. Barnard, 1866 March 20; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 March 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - Receipt to the Plymouth Coal Company, 1866 March 23; Hern, William (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 March 27; Thurlow, S. L. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 March 31; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 April 4; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 April 15; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to S. H. Sweet, 1866 May 8; Sheafer, P. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 May 9; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 May 9; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 9; Sumner, Charles (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 May 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - Estes Howe to Peter Lesley, 1866 May 12 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 15; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 May 16; Henry, Joseph (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 May 16; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to S. H. Sweet, 1866 May 16; Sheafer, P. W. (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 17; Dana, James D. (James Dwight), 1813-1895 (Box 9)
  - to James Hall, 1866 May 17; Sheafer, P. W. (Box 9)
  - Estes Howe to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 19 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 21; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 22; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 23; Howe, Estes (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 24; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 May 25; Henry, Joseph (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 May 27; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - Report to Henry C. Carey on Coal Beds near Schickshinny., 1866 May 31; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 June 1; Hall, James (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 June 1; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 June 1; Reeves, Samuel J. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 June 4; Henry, Joseph (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 June 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 June 4; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 June 8; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 June 14; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 June 15; Safford, James M. (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 June 21; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 July 5; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. Peter Lesley, 1866 July 5; Wright, Chauncey (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 July 6; Safford, James M. (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 July 10; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 July 14; Andrews, Emma B., 1837-1922 (Box 9)
  - to Peter Lesley, 1866 July 19; Lesquereux, Leo, 1806-1889 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 July 27; Harden, J. W. (Box 9)
  - Report to the Spring Creek and Clarion Oil Company. Elk County, Penna., 1866 July; Lesley, J. P., (J. Peter), 1819-1903 (Box 9)
  - to J. P. Lesley, 1866 Aug. 12; Frazer, John Fries, 1812-1872 (Box 9)